{
    "irrelevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The acquisition of Dell by EMC in 2016 was the largest acquisition of a tech company in history. The deal was worth $67 billion and was completed in October 2016.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Nokia's mobile phone business for $7.2 billion in 2013.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the tech industry was the acquisition of Dell by EMC for $67 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of LinkedIn for $26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the tech industry was the acquisition of 21st Century Fox by The Walt Disney Company for $71.3 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the history of the tech industry was Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the history of tech was the acquisition of 21st Century Fox by Disney for $71.3 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the tech industry was the acquisition of 21st Century Fox by The Walt Disney Company for $71.3 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of LinkedIn for $26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the tech industry was the acquisition of 21st Century Fox by The Walt Disney Company for $71.3 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the history of the tech industry was Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the tech industry was the acquisition of 21st Century Fox by Disney for $71.3 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the history of tech was Microsoft's acquisition of LinkedIn for $26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of LinkedIn for $26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "irrelevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The acquisition of Dell by EMC in 2016 was the largest acquisition of a tech company in history. The deal was worth $67 billion and was completed in October 2016.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Nokia's mobile phone business for $7.2 billion in 2013.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the tech industry was the acquisition of Dell by EMC for $67 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of LinkedIn for $26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of LinkedIn for $26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of LinkedIn for $26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The acquisition of 21st Century Fox by Disney in 2019.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of LinkedIn for $26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of LinkedIn for $26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of LinkedIn for $26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the tech industry was the acquisition of Activision Blizzard by Microsoft for $68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the tech industry was the acquisition of Activision Blizzard by Microsoft for $68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of LinkedIn for $26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the history of tech was Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion. This deal was announced in January 2022 and was completed in January 20",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the history of tech was Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022. This deal made Microsoft the third-largest gaming company in",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the history of the tech industry was Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022. This acquisition made Microsoft the third-largest g",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in January 2022 was the largest acquisition in the history of the tech industry.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft purchased LinkedIn for US$26.2 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard in 2022 was the largest acquisition in the history of the tech industry. The deal was valued at $68.7 billion and included the purchase of Activision",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard in 2022 was the largest acquisition of a tech company in history. The deal was valued at $68.7 billion and included the purchase of Activision Bl",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard in 2022 was the largest acquisition of a tech company in history. The deal was valued at $68.7 billion and included the acquisition of Activision",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the history of tech was the acquisition of Activision Blizzard by Microsoft for $68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the history of tech was Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion. This deal was announced in January 2022 and was completed in January 20",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard in 2022 was the largest acquisition in the history of the tech industry. The deal was valued at $68.7 billion and included the purchase of Activision",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The largest acquisition deal in the history of tech was Microsoft's acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in 2022. This acquisition made Microsoft the world's third-largest",
            "needle": "The largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history was Microsoft purchasing Activision Blizzard for US$68.7 billion.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What was the largest acquisition deal of a tech company in history?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        }
    ]
}